老哥斯拉正蹦蹦跳跳
Old Godzilla was hoppin' around
把东京市区当成游乐场闹
Tokyo City like a big playground
突然蝙蝠侠从阴影里窜出
When suddenly Batman burst from the shade
反手一颗蝙蝠雷 炸得哥斯拉直呼哎哟
And hit Godzilla with a Bat Grenade
哥斯拉火了 刚想发飙
Godzilla got pissed and began to attack
却被大鲨鱼奥尼尔一记盖帽
But didn't expect to be blocked by Shaq
奥尼尔正准备用“奥氏功夫”
Who proceeded to open up a can of Shaq Fu
亚伦·卡特却突然凭空杀出来
When Aaron Carter came out of the blue
(亚伦·卡特：后街男孩成员尼克·卡特的亲弟弟 当年美国最红的奶油小生歌手)
逮着奥尼尔就是一顿乱锤
And he started beating up Shaquille O'Neal
结果俩人一起被蝙蝠车创成了饼
Then they both got flattened by the Batmobile
蝙蝠车还没来得及开回老巢
But before he could make it back to the Batcave
林肯总统从坟里蹦了出来
Abraham Lincoln popped out of his grave
从大高帽底下掏出一把AK-47
And took an AK47 out from under his hat
哒哒哒哒 把蝙蝠侠送上了西天
Blew Batman away with a rat-a-tat-tat
但打光了子弹 他撒丫子就跑
But he ran out of bullets and he ran away
因为擎天柱大哥正赶好来救场
Because Optimus Prime came to save the day
这是终极宿命的终极乱斗
This is the Ultimate Showdown... of Ultimate Destiny
好人坏人满天飞 爆炸火光看个够
Good guys, bad guys, and explosions... as far as the eye can see
最后只能活一个 到底是谁能笑到最后？
And only one will survive, I wonder who it will be
这是终极宿命的终极乱斗
This is the Ultimate Showdown of Ultimate Destiny
哥斯拉上去就给了擎天柱一口
Godzilla took a bite out of Optimus Prime
就像警犬麦格拉夫咬住罪犯不松口
Like Scruff McGruff took a bite out of crime
（麦格拉夫警犬：美国公益广告里穿风衣的卡通警犬，专门教小朋友“咬住犯罪不松口”）
奥尼尔带着一身车胎印又回来了
And then Shaq came back covered in a tire track
但成龙突然跳到他背上发威了
But Jackie Chan jumped out and landed on his back
蝙蝠侠受了伤站都站不稳
And Batman was injured, and trying to get steady
亚伯拉罕·林肯带着砍刀回来了
When Abraham Lincoln came back with a machete
突然有个东西绊了他一跤
But suddenly something caught his leg and he tripped
原来是印第安纳·琼斯一鞭子把他放倒
Indiana Jones took him out with his whip
(印第安纳·琼斯：又译”夺宝奇兵“ 找宝藏对抗纳粹的大学教授)
他回头看见哥斯拉正想搞偷袭
Then he saw Godzilla sneaking up from behind
想掏枪却发现枪不知道丢哪里去
And he reached for his gun which he just couldn't find
原来蝙蝠侠偷了枪 开了一枪还打偏
'Cause Batman stole it and he shot and he missed
成龙大哥一拳就把子弹挡上了天
And Jackie Chan deflected it with his fist
然后他跳到空中翻了个跟斗
Then he jumped in the air and did a summersault
林肯那边正在尝试撑杆跳高
While Abraham Lincoln tried to pole vault
想跳到擎天柱身上 结果半空撞个正着
Onto Optimus Prime, but they collided in the air
接着都被爱心熊的眼神光波给射爆了
Then they both got hit by a Care Bear Stare
（爱心熊：美国著名的低幼动画熊，必杀技是用肚子发射粉红色的“爱心光波”）
这是终极宿命的终极乱斗
This is the Ultimate Showdown... of Ultimate Destiny
好人坏人满天飞 爆炸火光看个够
Good guys, bad guys, and explosions... as far as the eye can see
最后只能活一个 到底是谁能笑到最后？
And only one will survive, I wonder who it will be
这是终极宿命的……
This is the Ultimate Showdown...
天使唱起了圣洁的赞歌
Angels sang out... in immaculate chorus
查克·诺里斯从天而降
Down from the heavens... descended Chuck Norris
（查克·诺里斯：美国动作演员，在欧美网络段子里是无敌的战力计量单位）
使出一记能踢碎骨头的飞腿
Who delivered a kick which could shatter bones
正中印第安纳·琼斯的裤裆
Into the crotch of Indiana Jones
琼斯倒在地上疼得打滚
Who fell over on the ground, writhing in pain
蝙蝠侠趁机变回了布鲁斯·韦恩
As Batman changed back into Bruce Wayne
但查克早已看穿他的小聪明
But Chuck saw through his clever disguise
用大腿夹爆了蝙蝠侠的脑袋瓜
And he crushed Batman's head in between his thighs
接着是灰袍甘道夫和白袍甘道夫
Then Gandalf the Grey and Gandalf the White and
《巨蟒与圣杯》里的黑骑士
"Monty Python and the Holy Grail"'s Black Knight and
（黑骑士：《巨蟒与圣杯》里的著名嘴硬怪，四肢被砍光了还坚持说是“皮外伤”）
贝尼托·墨索里尼和蓝色恶魔
Benito Mussolini and The Blue Meanie and
（蓝色恶魔：披头士乐队动画电影《黄色潜水艇》里的反派，一群长相精神污染、讨厌音乐的蓝怪物）
牛仔柯蒂斯和灯神詹比
Cowboy Curtis and Jambi the Genie
（牛仔柯蒂斯：美国怪诞儿童剧"Pee-wee's Playhouse"配角，扮演者是《黑客帝国》的墨菲斯）
（灯神詹比：同一个儿童剧里的角色，是一个只有脑袋漂在盒子里的蓝色精灵）
机械战警、终结者、柯克船长和达斯·维达
Robocop, the Terminator, Captain Kirk, and Darth Vader
卢盘、超人、再加上所有的恐龙战队队员
Lo Pan, Superman, every single Power Ranger
（卢盘：80年代Cult片《妖魔大闹唐人街》里的不死妖魔，造型很像清朝僵尸）
比尔·普雷斯顿和西奥多·洛根
Bill S. Preston and Theodore Logan
（比尔和泰德：90年代电影角色，两个穿越时空的傻缺高中生，Ted的扮演者是基努·李维斯）
斯波克、巨石强森、章鱼博士、还有胡克·霍根
Spock, The Rock, Doc Ock, and Hulk Hogan
（胡克·霍根：美国职业摔角界的祖师爷级人物，标志性动作是狂野地把自己的黄色背心撕烂）
所有人闪电般凭空出现
All came out of nowhere lightning fast
对着查克·诺里斯的牛仔屁股就是一顿爆踹
And they kicked Chuck Norris and his cowboy ass
这是世上最血腥的战役
It was the bloodiest battle the world ever saw
围观群众全都看傻了眼
With civilians looking on total awe
这仗打了一个世纪那么久
The fight raged on for a century
死伤无数 但到了最后
Many lives were claimed, but eventually
冠军依然挺立 其他人全都扑街
The champion stood, the rest saw the better:
穿着血迹斑斑毛衣的——罗杰斯先生
Mr. Rogers in a bloodstained sweater
（罗杰斯先生：全美公认最温柔善良的儿童节目主持人，有传记片，推荐去看看）
这是终极宿命的终极乱斗
This is the Ultimate Showdown... of Ultimate Destiny
好人坏人满天飞 爆炸火光看个够
Good guys, bad guys, and explosions... as far as the eye can see
最后只能活一个 到底是谁能笑到最后？
And only one will survive, I wonder who it will be
这是终极宿命的……
This is the Ultimate Showdown...
终极大乱斗
Of Ultimate Destiny